Well, nesting um functions inside of
each other, it can get out of hand. And
this is code that I had CHIGBT generate
cuz there was no way I was writing this
myself. Um yuck. Um and honestly, if
Chad GBT ever goes terminator, I will
probably be on a hit list for this. Um
but this is having your computer wait
various amounts of time and then logging
out exactly how long it waited. Um and
it's waiting an additional amount of
time each time. And if you're struggling
to read this, good. This is a pain.
Nobody wants to read this. But in the
past, this was the only way to deal with
asynchronous code. And you may think,
well, when would I ever need to deal
with it like that? Well, I had an app
that I built. And in that app, you
needed to make a request to the Genius
API. Or in other words, I needed to make
a request with song lyrics. And then the
resource would give me back a list of
song names. I then took those song names
and sent them to Spotify. So that would
be asynchronous functions nested in
asynchronous functions. I had to wait
for my first data to come back before I
could send the second data. And in the
past, I would have had to code something
like this monstrosity. And so let's all
take a moment of silence for the
developers who only had this as an
option for years.
Okay, that's a long enough moment of
silence. Um, fortunately, there are
things that will make our lives better.
Um they are our white Bronx.